# Albert Grimmett Jr

Gilbert, WV 25621 ajgrimmett23@gmail.com +1 304 784 7578

Freelance Web Developer and Frontend Developer for over 3 years. Attended a coding bootcamp for a while but mainly self-learning from udemy courses. Enjoy being creative, taking on challenging tasks, making ideas come to life, and learning new and improved skills

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

## **Web Developer**

Freelance - Logan, WV January 2019 to Present

Planned and built responsive websites from start to finish while interacting with clients during the building process. Used Html5,CSS3,LESS,Bootstrap,JS,PHP, React-Bootstrap, and React to build websites. Used Adobe Express to optimize photos I took, stock photos, and/or photos/videos the client already had.

## **Assistant Manager**

Hawks River Lodge - Gilbert, WV May 2015 to August 2016

I filed paperwork and did scheduling. Also helped customers with any issues. Sold some retail among sweaters, shirts, sweat pants, shoes and backpacks.

## Education

## High school diploma

Logan Senior High School - Logan, WV September 2011 to June 2015

## Skills

- HTML5 (4 years)
- CSS3 (4 years)
- GitHub (4 years)
- Git (3 years)
- Python (1 year)
- JavaScript (3 years)
- Node.js (2 years)
- Less (3 years)

- Bootstrap (2 years)
- MongoDB (1 year)
- MySQL (1 year)
- Angular (1 year)
- TypeScript (2 years)
- React (1 year)
- React Native (1 year)
- Negotiation
- Customer Service (1 year)
- PHP (1 year)
- Express.js (1 year)
- Adobe Express (1 year)
- AWS (1 year)
- Sales
- User Interface (UI)
- Canva (2 years)
- Adobe Photoshop (1 year)

### Links

http://Ajgrimmett.netlify.app

https://github.com/aj-grimmett

https://www.linkedin.com/in/albert-grimmett-jr-57569b165

#### Certifications and Licenses

## **Udemy Web Developer Certification**

February 2020 to Present

Completed Web Developer Udemy course by Colt Steele

#### Assessments

## Sales skills — Proficient

May 2023

Influencing and negotiating with customers

Full results: Proficient

#### Attention to detail — Proficient

December 2022

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information

Full results: Proficient

## **Software developer fit — Proficient**

August 2022

Measures the traits that are important for successful software developers

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.